Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXVII is arranged in 48 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXVII. FEDERATIONS AND COUNCILS
  - Sub-Series 274-1. Federations and Councils
    - Eastern Federation. Annual Meeting, 1923 (Box 253, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 274-2. Federations and Councils
    - Eastern Federation. Resolution. 1921 (Box 253, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 274-3. Federations and Councils
    - Texas Federation. Texas Federationist, 1922 (Box 253, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 274-4. Federations and Councils
    - Missouri Federation, 1928 (Box 253, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 274-5. Federations and Councils
    - Buffalo District Council, 1922-1935 (Box 253, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 274-6. Federations and Councils
    - Alexandria and Washington District Council, 1921 (Box 253, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 274-8. Federations and Councils
    - Nebraska Legislative Board -1921 (Box 253, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 274-9. Federations and Councils
    - Altoona Advisory Board, 1921 (Box 253, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 274-10. Federations and Councils
    - California State Federation, 1920-1922 (Box 253, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 274-12. Federations and Councils
    - Proposed Bureau of Inspection, 1921 (Box 253, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 274-13. Federations and Councils
    - Columbus District Council, 1921-1937 (Box 253, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 274-14. Federations and Councils
    - Ohio State Federation, 1922-1927 (Box 253, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 274-15. Federations and Councils
    - Chicago District Council, 1955-1957 (Box 253b, Folder 1)
    - Chicago District Council, 1951-1954 (Box 253b, Folder 2)
      November 1951-December 1954.
    - Chicago District Council, 1948-1951 (Box 253b, Folder 3)
      October 1948-October 1951.
    - Chicago District Council, 1945-1948 (Box 253b, Folder 4)
      1945-September 1948.
    - Chicago District Council, 1941-1944 (Box 253b, Folder 5)
    - Chicago District Council, 1921-1940 (Box 253b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 274-16. Federations and Councils
    - Niagara Frontier Council, 1921-1922 (Box 253b, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 274-17. Federations and Councils
    - Twin Cities District Council, 1921-1951 (Box 253b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 274-18. Federations and Councils
    - New Orleans District Council, 1934-1953 (Box 253b, Folder 9)
    - New Orleans District Council, 1921-1933 (Box 253b, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 274-19. Federations and Councils
    - Toledo Joint Council, 1933-1940 (Box 253b, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 274-20. Federations and Councils
    - Cleveland District Council, 1922-1954 (Box 253b, Folder 12)
    - Cleveland District Council -Shippers and Receivers Guide and Traffic Directory, 1923 (Box 253b, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 274-21. Federations and Councils
    - Western Pennsylvania Council, 1922 (Box 253b, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 274-22. Federations and Councils
    - Minneapolis Joint Activities Committee, 1924-1957 (Box 253b, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 274-23. Federations and Councils
    - Greater Kansas City District Council, 1926-1941 (Box 253b, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 274-24. Federations and Councils
    - New Orleans District Council, 1922 (Box 253b, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 274-25. Federations and Councils
    - Indianapolis District Council, 1928-1934 (Box 253b, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 274-26. Federations and Councils
    - Cincinnati District Council, 1928-1942 (Box 253b, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 274-27. Federations and Councils
    - Detroit District Council, 1929-1950 (Box 253b, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 274-28. Federations and Councils
    - Buffalo District Council, 1930-1941 (Box 253b, Folder 21)
    - Buffalo District Council, 1929 (Box 253b, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 274-29. Federations and Councils
    - New England District Council, 1929 (Box 253b, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 274-30. Federations and Councils
    - New England District Council, 1930 (Box 253b, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 274-31. Federations and Councils
    - St. Louis and East St. Louis District Council, 1930-1946 (Box 253b, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 274-32. Federations and Councils
    - Springfield Council, 1930 (Box 253b, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 274-33. Federations and Councils
    - Louisville District Council, 1930-1932 (Box 253b, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 274-34. Federations and Councils
    - Joint Conference Committee, New York City Railway Express Employees, 1931 (Box 253b, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 274-35. Federations and Councils
    - Iowa State Federation, 1931 (Box 253b, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 274-36. Federations and Councils
    - Boston District Council, 1932 (Box 253b, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 274-37. Federations and Councils
    - East St. Louis Standard Railroad District Council, 1932 (Box 253b, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 274-38. Federations and Councils
    - Milwaukee District Council -1935-1957 (Box 253b, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 274-40. Federations and Councils
    - Jacksonville District Council, 1937-1950 (Box 253b, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 274-41. Federations and Councils
    - Jersey City District Council, 1937 (Box 253b, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 274-42. Federations and Councils
    - Toronto District Council, 1938 (Box 253b, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 274-44. Federations and Councils
    - Baltimore District Council -1939-1946 (Box 253b, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 274-46. Federations and Councils
    - Houston District Council, 1941-1942 (Box 253b, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 274-47. Federations and Councils
    - Fort Worth District Council, 1943-1953 (Box 253b, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 274-48. Federations and Councils
    - Miami District Council, 1947-1948 (Box 253b, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 274-50. Federations and Councils
    - New Orleans Joint Council of Lodges, 1950-1953 (Box 253b, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 274-51. Federations and Councils
    - Atlanta District Council, 1950-1951 (Box 253b, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 274-52. Federations and Councils
    - Victoria Building Trades Council. Vancouver Island District, 1952 (Box 253b, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 274-53. Federations and Councils
    - Los Angeles District Council, 1952-1957 (Box 253b, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 274-54. Federations and Councils
    - Pittsburgh Joint Activities Committee, 1955 (Box 253b, Folder 44)